WE COMPILE AND SEE THE NAME OF EXECUTABLE
For using the console in windows is neccessary to go to the command prompt of visual basic
After that, we access to the compile directory and verify that the executable is there
The program wait for a directory with 3 files named mask, source, and target
The mask show in white the portion of image source that will use
here we verify that images has the same size
Program wait for the directory with the files image source, target and mask and the name of the result image
If i would like to use the mixed gradient, is neccesary to write the parameter -m before of the directory parameter
Here is the result  of mixed gradient compare  with the normal gradient
Look that the normal gradient is more evident the mask that i used in the final result
MERCI, GRACIAS, THANK YOU